AMR ABU-ALEZZ — " CUSTOMER CARE "

Q Cairo - EGYPT

U 01142750475

@ Ezzamr577@gmail.com

Www.abual3zz.com

in Amr-abo-elezz-526890290

Responsibility

Marketing

Team working

Problem solving

Decision making

Communication Skills

Listening and Speaking

Time management skills

Word & Excel & PowerPoint

Interests:

Business Management

Learning constantly

Self development

Programming

Make friends

Help others

Marketing

Languages:

1st /e Arabic C 2



2nd / English A 2

3rd / German 🛕 📶

Introduction About Me:

My name is Amr. I am now 26 years old. I was born in El-Minya, But I live in Cairo, I have abachelor of arts, Archaeology Department from faculty of arts at Alminia university, then I have been granted a final exemption from military service. Now I'm working as a pharmacist assistant in El-Ezaby pharmacies, I have experience in the pharmaceutical field, dealing with customers directly or over the phone and receiving orders

Experience:

El-Ezaby pharmacies

Pharmacist assistant

2021 - Until

Pharmacist assistant at El-Ezaby pharmacies

Destra Pharma Company 2019 - 2021

Pharmacist Assistant

Pharmacist Assistant at Destra Pharma Company

the Forza Pharma pharmaceutical company 2018 - 2019

Pharmacist Assistant

Pharmacist assistant at Forza Pharma

Chipsy 2018 - 2018

Data entry

data entry at Chipsy Company

2016 - 2018

Free-lancer

Freelancer at Khamsat Foundation

Micro Engineering

Ai " Specialist "

Ai " Virtual Assistant " at Micro Engineering Company .

Education:

Faculty of Arts , Elminia University 2021

Debartment of arcology

+ Using Computer:

Excellent at using a computer

Excellent in using Excel and PowerPoint

h